《绿箭》前情提要
Previously, on "Arrow"...
你敢动  我就割开你的喉咙
Twitch, and I will open your throat.
斯莱德·威尔逊
Slade Wilson.
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen.
那就让我教你怎么活下来
Let me show you how not to die.
或许你内心里还是名斗士
There might be a fighter inside of you after all.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉什么
For what?
抱歉没告诉你我真实的感受
For not telling you how I really feel.
是时候做出选择了  奥利弗  选出谁生谁死
Time to choose, Oliver, who lives and who dies.
不要  不要
No! No!
不
No!
不管是谁做的
Whoever did this to her
我要他血债血偿
is going to suffer.
在你了解什么叫彻底绝望前
You cannot die until you have known...
我不会让你死的
complete despair.
你会了解的  我向你承诺
And you will. I promise.
我们一直追踪的一个人
There's a new player we've been tracking.
我们一直叫他丧钟
We've been calling him Deathstroke.
斯莱德的目的是利用米拉库鲁建立一支人体武器部队
Slade's goal is to create an army of human weapons using the the Mirakuru.
我阻止不了他做任何事情
I can't stop him from doing anything.
五年前  我对你做出过一项承诺
Five years ago, I made you a promise.
我是来兑现承诺的
I'm here to fulfill it.
这件事结束之前  还有一个人
There is still one person who has to die
必须得死
before this can end.
奥利弗
Oliver.
奥利弗  你没事吧
Oliver, man, you ok?
解药不管用
The cure's not working.
我们不能确定
We don't know that.
他体内还有很多西藏蝮蛇毒
He still has a lot of Tibetan pit viper venom in his system.
那是什么
What's that?
敌人逼近警告
Proximity alarm.
我将塔和感应器连接
I rigged the tower with sensors
以防斯莱德的手下来追杀我们
just in case Slade's goons came here to kill us.
斯莱德的手下来追杀我们了
Slade's goons are here to kill us.
告诉我详情  费利西蒂
Talk to me, Felicity.
他们进来了  就在我们下方
They're inside, they're right underneath us.
我在哪里
Where am I?
费利西蒂
Felicity!
从缆绳下去
Down the cable!
快
Go.
快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
天啊
Oh, my god!
出什么事了
What the hell happened?
是斯莱德的大军  你说得对  这地方的确暴露了
Slade's army. You were right about this place being compromised.
莱拉  你老板要在黎明时炸掉这座城市
Lyla, your boss is going to bomb the city at dawn.
沃勒觉得所有问题
Yeah, Waller's never seen a problem she didn't think
都能用无人机解决
couldn't be solved with a drone strike.
你觉得我为什么过来
Why do you think I'm here?
你知道沃勒要
You knew Waller was
把城市夷为平地  但你还是来了
looking to level the city and you came here anyway?
你在这里
You're here.
你得回超能力联合调查组
You need to go back to A.R.G.U.S.
你得阻止沃勒
You need to stop Waller
或者给我们争取到足够时间来阻止斯莱德
or buy us enough time to stop Slade.
我也去  至死不渝  对吧
Not without me. Till death do us part, right?
这次也许真会死的
This time it might.
两位  我需要你们搜寻尽可能多的武器
Guys? I need you to scrounge as many weapons as you can find,
特别是注射箭
especially injection arrows.
我们要把里面装满解药  那显然有效
We're going to fill them with the cure-- which clearly works--
这事今晚就能结束  不伤一人
and this ends tonight, without killing.
已经死了够多人了
There's been enough death already.
不
No!
西娅
Thea.
这叫防弹衣
It's called Kevlar.
如果你要杀了我  就...
If you're going to kill me, just...
赶快动手
get it over with.
杀了你  为什么  因为你对我开枪吗
Kill you? Why? Because you shot me?
我很高兴你这样做
I'm glad you did.
你有病吧
You're sick.
也许吧
Perhaps.
不然还怎么解释  不到一年前
How else to explain the fact that not a year ago,
你哥哥也拿着一把枪指着我
your brother held a gun to my face as well.
汤米
Tommy?
他缺乏信仰  没有扣动扳机的勇气
He lacked conviction. The strength to pull the trigger,
但你不一样  西娅
but not you, Thea.
你是铁打的  你真是我的女儿
You are made of iron. You are truly my daughter,
我无比骄傲
and I could not be more proud.
记住你的训练
Remember your training.
聪明点  一枪命中
You be smart, you take clean shots,
不要错过...
and you don't miss the--
退到梅尔策大道
Fall back to Meltzer Avenue.
联合广场需要特种部队  市政厅成了一片废墟
We need SWAT at Union Plaza. City hall's a crater.
他们无处不在
They're--they're everywhere!
撤退  撤退  我中弹了
Fall back, fall back, I'm hit!
听着  我知道你们很害怕
Ok, listen, I know you're scared.
如果不怕  那就不是正常人了
You wouldn't be human if you weren't.
但今晚  这座城市  我们的城市
But tonight, this city, our city...
指望着你们每一个人
It's counting on each and every one of you.
所以派你们去  你们就是英雄
So you go out there and you be the heroes,
我知道你们都是英雄
I know you all to be.
行动
Go.
你妹妹呢
Where's your sister?
-我也不知道  -探长
- I don't know. - Detective.
我已经跟警察局广场连上了
I've got one-p-p on the line,
这样在实战中  你就是最高指挥官
with it, pike in the field, you're the ranking officer.
你去吧  我去找莎拉
You should go. I'll find Sara.
听着  我希望你别离开警察保护区域  懂吗
Listen, I don't want you step outside this precinct, you hear me?
我不离开  我保证
I won't. I promise.
很好  宝贝
All right sweet heart.
汇报情况
What do we got?
别把我姐姐卷进来
My sister can't be a part of this.
-我不希望她受伤  -莎拉
- I don't want her getting hurt. - Sara!
-怎么回事  -劳蕾尔
- What's going on? - Laurel...
看来很多事我都不记得了
Well, it seems like I missed a lot.
你都记得什么
Well, what do you remember?
我记得我出城  要去布鲁德海文
Leaving town and heading to Bludhaven.
我一直神志不清吗
Was I out cold the whole time?
费利西蒂
Felicity.
是的
You were out.
你一直神志不清
The whole time.
斯莱德至少有五十个左右人体武器
Slade has at least 50 or so of those human weapons.
如果打算对他们使用解药  我们需要支军队
We'll need a whole army if we plan on hitting 'em with the cure.
我知道
I know.
所以我才带了一支军队过来
Which is why an army is what I've brought.
莎拉  带这么多人来之前你应该先打个电话
Gee, Sara, you could have called before you invited...
五  六  七个杀手跑到我们的秘密藏身处来了
5, 6, 7 assassins down into our top secret lair.
她来干嘛
What is she doing here?
是我请她来的
I asked her to come.
我叫妮莎  拉斯·厄尔·高福的女儿
I'm Nyssa, daughter of Ra's Al Ghul.
恶魔的后裔
Heir to the demon.
费利西蒂·斯莫克  麻省理工学院09年毕业生
Felicity smoak. MIT class of '09.
这就是你去的地方吗  南达尔巴特
This is where you went? Nanda Parbat?
杀手联盟  他们都是雇佣兵
The league of assassins? These people are mercenaries, sara.
不管他们承诺了什么  都要付出代价
Whatever they promised you, it comes at a price.
你不用担心这个  因为我已经付出过了
You don't have to worry about it, because I've already paid it.
你答应要回去
You agreed to go back.
我不会让斯莱德·威尔逊伤害劳蕾尔或我爸爸
Look, I'm not going to let Slade Wilson hurt Laurel or my father.
为了保护我爱的人
And I'm willing to do whatever it takes
我愿意做任何事
to keep the ones that I love safe.
而且我希望你也准备好做同样的事
And I hope you're ready to do the same.
特别是经历了一切之后
Especially after what happened.
奥利  你妈妈的事我很遗憾
Ollie, I'm sorry about your mother.
我也愿意不惜一切代价
I am willing to do whatever it takes,
但那不意味着冷血的杀戮才是解决办法
but that doesn't mean cold-blooded killing is the answer,
莎拉  我们有解药了
Sara. We have the cure now.
要跟超乎想象的事战斗
To fight the unthinkable,
就必须用超乎想象的手段
you have to be willing to do the unthinkable.
奎恩先生  你也许不想得到我的帮助
You may not want my help, Mr. Queen,
但有些小问题是你们急需解决的
But there's little question you are in desperate need of it.
首先我们必须找到斯莱德的运行基地
First we need to find Slade's base of operations.
斯莱德·威尔逊和莎贝尔·罗切夫
Slade Wilson and Isabel Rochev are using
正用你之前的办公楼  来当做运行基地
your former office building as their base of operations.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
我准备好做些补偿了
Ready to serve up some payback.
牢牢记住训练的内容
Then remember your training.
记住学过的所有内容
Remember everything that you've learned.
你是认真的吗
Are--are you for real?
有人...一位朋友
Someone--a friend--
曾告诉我  如果你通过了严酷的考验
once told me that if you survive a crucible,
你会因此而强大
you grow the stronger for it.
这个可以作为提醒
This is to remind you of that.
西娅怎么样了  她还好吗
What happened to Thea? Is she...ok?
她很好  这一切开始之前
She's fine. She was headed out of the city
她就离开了
before this started.
要按我说的做
We do this my way.
联盟从不活捉俘虏
The league does not take prisoners.
今晚是个例外
It does tonight.
西娅  外面很危险
Thea, it's dangerous out there.
总比跟我的变态恶棍爸爸在一起好
Better than here with my psycho-villain dad,
我要杀他  他居然很开心
who's happy I tried to kill him.
罗伊
Roy?
西娅  是我
Thea, it's-- it's me.
我只是想确认你一切都好
I just wanted to make sure you were all right.
我很好  我在火车站
I'm fine. I'm at the train station.
西娅  听我说
Thea, listen to me.
你在那里不安全  你能不能到我那见个面
You're not safe there. Can you please meet me at my place?
我会来的
I'll be there.
我尽快
Soon as I can.
好的  注意安全
Ok, be safe.
是谁打来的
Who was that?
罗伊吗
Roy?
你是我女儿  你的很多事我都知道
You're my daughter. There's not much I don't know about you.
真有趣  决定逃避所有谎言
Interesting how you run back to him
和掺假的真相之后  你竟然要回到他身边
after resolving to run away to escape all the lies
他也没什么区别  西娅
and half-truths. He's no different, Thea.
跟你妈妈和奥利弗没区别
No different from your mother or Oliver.
如果你不相信我
If you don't believe me,
那你就去找他
then you should go to him.
我会的
I will.
如果你再跟着我  我就再打你一枪
And if you try to follow me, I'll shoot you again.
你需要的时候我会出现的
When you need me, I'll be there.
电梯安全了
Elevator bank's clear.
会议室安全
Conference room's clear.
你们敢自己来
You must have quite a bit
一定是对解药很有信心
of faith in this cure if you've come alone.
我们不是自己来的
We didn't come alone.
莎拉  别
Sara, don't!
杀我或不杀我
Kill me. Don't kill me.
都无所谓
It doesn't matter.
我打败了你  我夺走了
I beat you. I took away the one--
你不愿做必要的事
Your reticence to do what is necessary
正是星城受到攻击的原因
is why your city burns.
这样行不通
This isn't working.
我没办法接近斯莱德给他注射解药
I can't get close enough to Slade to hit him with the cure.
那我们怎么办
So what do we do?
又一个失败了
Another disappointment!
下一个
Bring me another!
斯莱德  你在干什么
Come on, Slade, what are you doing?!
促进科学事业
Advancing the cause of science.
等等  我知道莎朵的死你怪我
Wait, no, no, wait, I know you blame me for Shado's death!
-我也怪我自己  -他就该这样
- I blame myself! - He should!
我们不能在一起都是因为他
It's his fault we aren't together.
你说过我们是兄弟
You said once that we were brothers.
现在  我以兄弟的身份
And right now, I am begging you,
请求你  听我说一句
brother to brother, just listen to me!
别听他的  他说的都是谎话
Don't listen to him! All his words are lies.
要不是你  我已经死了
I wouldn't be alive right now if it wasn't for you.
要不是他  我现在还活着
I would be alive if it wasn't for him.
想想莎朵
Think about Shado!
她关心我们两个人
She--she cared for both of us.
她不会想看这一切发生
She wouldn't want this.
她希望我们能离开炼狱
She wants us off Lian Yu.
她会希望这一切结束
She'd want all of this to end!
他说得对  这一切必须结束
He's right! This needs to end.
你得杀了他
You need to kill him.
已经两小时了
Two hours now.
对不起  我的朋友
Prosti menya, moy drug.
对不起了  奥利弗
I'm sorry, Oliver.
动手吧
Do it.
斯莱德  不要
Slade, no!
扣动扳机
Pull the trigger!
斯莱德
Slade!
劳蕾尔  劳蕾尔
Laurel! Laurel!
亲爱的  亲爱的
Sweetheart, sweetheart!
发生什么事了
What--what happened?!
-莎拉  -她走了  宝贝
- Sara! - She's gone, sweetie.
-天哪  -你还好吗
- Oh, my God. - You OK?
她和那个女人在一起
She's with that woman!
那个带走妈妈的女人
The woman that took mom.
不许动
Stay right here.
站住  不要向前走了
Stop right there! Don't take one more step.
不许动
One more step!
不要  不要
No, no!
导弹已经瞄准目标
Drone's locked on target.
瞄准星城
Starling City.
威尔逊为什么对奎恩家的人这么上火
Why does this Wilson guy have such a mad-on for the Queens?
我不知道  还好
I don't know. It's a good thing
西娅和奥利弗及时出城了
Thea and Oliver got out of town in time.
所以他们就对我们家下手吗
So they have to go after my family?
她在这里做什么
What's she doing here?
她是来帮忙的
She's here to help.
请相信我
Just trust me, please.
我好像得跟任何能帮我
I guess today I'll have to work with anybody
救回女儿的人合作了
who can help get my daughter back.
什么
What?
一个戴面具的人抓走了劳蕾尔
One of these masked guys, they took Laurel.
我没能阻止他们
I--I couldn't stop them.
相信我  我尽力了
Believe me, I-- I tried.
我们有一个新的大麻烦
Oh, we have a new, big problem.
相比我们的其他问题  这个更加严重
Which, considering our other ones, is really saying something.
我黑了一个卫星  用来做热成像
I hacked a satellite and tasked it for thermographic imaging--
斯莱德手下所有人都聚集到了乔达诺隧道
All of Slade's men are gathering at the Giordano Tunnel.
我以为这些人是想
I thought these guys were
毁了这座城市  而不是逃跑
trying to destroy the city, not escape it.
超能力联合调查组要夷平星城
A.R.G.U.S. is going to level the city
以阻止他们逃出去
to stop them from getting out.
这样正中斯莱德的下怀  他知道沃勒的计划
That's what Slade's planning on. He knows Waller's tactics.
幸运的是  由于斯莱德的人
Fortunately, with Slade's men
想通过隧道离开
attempting to leave via the tunnel,
我们所有的目标都集中在一起了
all our targets will be grouped in a single place.
我们得攻下那里  召集你的手下
We need to take it. Gather your men.
劳蕾尔怎么办  威尔逊抓走她一定是有原因
What about Laurel? Wilson took her for a reason.
我知道是什么原因
I know what it is.
但是星城更加重要
But the city comes first.
她是我的女儿  你的姐姐
This is my daughter. This is your sister!
你们不能就这么不管她
You can't just leave her like this!
我知道你想要
Look, I know you said you
尝试新的方法  我尊重你的决定
were trying another way, and I respect that.
但是斯莱德·威尔逊和他的手下
But Slade Wilson? His men?
他们是怪物
They're monsters.
怪物需要被摧毁
And monsters, they need to be destroyed.
你以前杀过人
You've killed before.
今晚我建议你重拾起这个习惯
Tonight, I suggest you get back in the habit.
他说得不对
He's wrong.
他是对的
He's right.
我失去了一切全都是因为
I've lost everything because I'm fighting Slade Wilson
我总是对斯莱德·威尔逊手下留情
with one hand tied behind my back.
这个人谋杀了我母亲
The man murdered my mother.
我一定要杀了他
I have to kill him.
你说你曾经做出过选择
You told me you had a choice.
几年前你本来可以救斯莱德
That years ago, you could have
但是你选择杀了他
cured Slade but you chose to kill him instead.
现在所发生的这一切不是因为你手下留情
This isn't happening because you're not willing to be a killer;
而是因为你曾经就想杀他
It's happening because you were one.
你说得对  事情是这样的开始的
You're right. That's how this started.
也该这样结束
It's how it has to end.
除了杀他我现在没有其它选择
The only move that he has left for me is to kill him.
我救不了他  抓不到他
I can't cure him, I can't capture him,
我甚至不能以智取胜
I can't even out-think him!
那就不要  不要
Then don't. Don't...
让他以智取胜吧
Just make him out-think you.
市民们被要求待在家中
Residents are being urged to stay in their homes.
未经证实的谣言称
Amidst unconfirmed rumors
市长本人也出现在
that mayor blood is among the casualties
恐怖袭击的伤亡名单上
as masked men terrorize the city...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我为所有的事都感到抱歉
I'm sorry for everything.
我
I...
不  没关系
No, it's OK.
我知道  我知道在过去的几个月里
I know--I know that I haven't exactly
有时候我举止十分反常
been myself for the past few months.
我被注射了...
I was injected with...
某种药物  我知道
With some drug. I know.
辛告诉我了
Sin told me.
你现在恢复了吗
But are you OK now?
是的  我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我在这里醒过来
I woke up here.
我错过了很多时间  但是
I lost a lot of time, but...
那绿箭呢
And what about the Arrow?
他说他要照顾你的
He said he was going to take care of you?
绿箭的事我一无所知
I don't know anything about the Arrow.
我再也不关心那些了  但是我
I'm done with all of that, but I...
你是我唯一关心的人
You're the only person that I've ever cared about.
你还好吗  发生什么事了吗
Are you okay? Did something happen to you?
没什么
It doesn't matter.
我们  我们离开这吧
Look, let's just-- let's just get out of here.
我们重新开始
Let's start over.
我们可以成为我们想成为的人
We can be whoever we want to
不受别人的干扰
without anyone getting in our way.
我再也不要失去你了
I'm never losing you again.
费利西蒂：我们需要你
还有...
Yeah, there's just--
我们离开前我还有一件事需要处理
there's just one thing I need to take care of
留在这里  好吗
before we go, OK? So just stay here
打包些我们需要的东西  我很快就回来
and get some stuff packed and I'll be right back.
-不  罗伊  太危险了  -我知道
- No, Roy, it's dangerous. - I know.
但是我必须这么做
But I have to do this.
如果不去试一次的话我是不会甘心的
I wouldn't feel right if I left without trying.
你信任我吗
Do you trust me?
当然
Yes.
等我回来我们就永远离开这里
Then when I get back, we're getting out of here forever.
我爱你
I love you.
奥利弗
Oliver.
来这里干什么  整个城市都要毁了
What are we doing here? The whole city's falling apart.
我知道
I know.
你需要留在这里
You need to stay here.
什么
What?!
为什么  你不能请求我留在
Why? You can't just ask me to--
我不是在请求
I'm not asking.
等一切结束之后我会来这里找你
I will come and get you when this is all over.
-不  -费利西蒂
- No! - Felicity...
不行  除非你告诉我为什么
No! Not unless you tell me why.
因为我要保证你的安全
Because I need you to be safe.
但是我不想要安全
Well, I don't want to be safe.
我想和你待在一起
I want to be with you.
还有其他人也不安全
And the others, unsafe!
我不会让那种事情发生
I can't let that happen.
奥利弗
Oliver.
你这么做很不讲理
You're not making any sense.
斯莱德把劳蕾尔抓去
Slade took Laurel
因为他要杀掉我心爱的女人
because he wants to kill the woman I love.
我知道  所以呢
I know, so?
所以他抓错人了
So he took the wrong woman.
我爱你
I love you.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
明白
Yes.
约翰尼
Johnny.
怎么了
Yeah?
没什么
Never mind.
莱拉
Hey, Lyla.
你知道我爱你  是不是
I love you. You know that, right?
其实我知道
I do, actually.
但还是很喜欢听你这么说
But it's good to hear it.
抵达时间
Time to impact?
无人机52分钟后抵达目标
Drone is 52 minutes out from target.
接戈麦斯中士
Get me Sergeant Gomez.
E队无应答
Easy Company's not responding.
我要看视频信号
I need a visual.
他们在隧道里  长官  拍不到那里
They're in a tunnel, ma'am, I can't get a picture.
那隧道里发生了什么鬼事
What the hell is going on in that tunnel?
戈麦斯中士  快回答  戈麦斯中士
Sergeant Gomez, come in! Sergeant Gomez!
不要伤他们性命  让解药发挥作用
No kill shots. Let the cure do its work.
准备
Ready.
Ready!
准备  射箭
Ready, fire!
麦考斯探员  这个地区仅限有授权的。。。
Agent Michaels, this area's restricted to all unauthorized--
搞什么鬼呢  提前假释吗
What the hell is this? Early parole?
沃勒要炸平星城
Waller's looking to bomb Starling City.
需要你们帮忙来阻止她
We need your help to stop her.
虽然我很乐意向她展示下我们对她的看法
As much as I'd love to show the wall what we think of her,
但你别忘了我们会被炸死的
there's just that little matter of tick, tick, boom!
记得吗  我们脊椎里都埋了微型炸弹
OK? We've got all that miniature bombs in our spines.
你们都得相信我
You have to trust me.
还有  罗通  不许杀人
And Lawton, no dropping bodies.
好吧  一点乐趣都没了
Yeah, sure, take the fun out of it.
妮莎
Nyssa!
快跳船
Get off the ship!
你走我才走
Not without you!
快给我  把米拉库鲁给我
Give it to me! Give me the Mirakuru!
可恶
No!
奥利弗
Oliver!
莎拉
Sara!
-奥利  -莎拉
- Ollie! - Sara!
让无人机准备发射
Prep the drone to fire.
可是预定发射时间是六点
Weapon's hot was set for 06:00.
快给我准备发射
Prep the drone to fire!
趴下  马上
Down, now!
所有人都趴下  趴下
Everybody get down, down, down!
沃勒  马上叫停无人机
Waller, call that drone off!
你这是叛国罪  麦考斯探员
This is treason, Agent Michaels.
你让成千上万的生命陷入危险
Treason that risks hundreds of thousands of lives.
这一点你想过吗
Have you thought about that?
你想没想过
Have you thought about
你该怎么对你的儿子解释
how You're going to explain that to your son?
或者对你的女儿
Or is it your daughter?
是医生没告诉你  还是你不想知道
Did doctor specify, or did you want to keep it a surprise?
恭喜了  狄格尔先生  你要当父亲了
Congratulations, Mr. Diggle, you're going to be a father.
说
Go!
你忙得很啊  小子
You've been busy, kid.
结束了  斯莱德  你的军队完蛋了
It's over, Slade! Your army is broken.
我可怜这些狗腿子
And I pity them.
但你再次搞错重点了
But once again, you miss the point.
你的至爱在我手里
I have the one you love.
我要你到我指定的地方来见我
You're going to meet me where I say.
不然的话  我就杀了她
Otherwise, I'm going to kill her.
不  你想做什么随你  我不会再听你的了
No, you do what you have to. I'm done playing your games!
我让你不听  你才能不听
You're done when I say you're done!
我有点意外
I was surprised.
我一直以为你专恋强势的女人
I thought you had a thing for stronger women,
但我见到她之后
but now that I've met her...
我算明白为什么了
I can see the appeal.
她实在可爱
She is quite lovely...
你的费利西蒂
your Felicity.
你敢动  我就割开你的喉咙
Twitch, and I will open your throat.
这是我对你说的第一句话
My first words to you.
你还记得吗  我记得
Do you remember? I do.
我记得清清楚楚
I remember the exact moment.
我的刀刃抵在你的脖子上
My blade against your neck.
就如同现在我的刀架在你心爱之人的脖子上
Just like my blade is against the neck of your beloved.
如果我当初一刀杀了你
If only I'd killed you then,
一切就都不同了
everything would be different.
把弓放下  小子
Drop the bow, kid.
马上
Do it.
太好了
Yes.
无数个漫漫长夜
Countless nights dreaming
我都梦想着夺走你的一切来报复你
of taking from you all that you took from me.
-所以要杀死我最爱的人吗  -没错
- By killing the woman I love? - Yes.
就像你最爱的莎朵
Like you love Shado.
是的
Yes.
你现在能看见她
You see her.
是不是
Don't you?
她在你癫狂的脑子里是什么样子  斯莱德
Well, what does she look like in your madness, Slade?
她对你说了什么
What does she say to you?
在我的记忆里  她非常美丽
I remember her being beautiful.
又年轻  又善良
Young. Kind.
她一定会对你
She would be horrified
以她的名义所做的一切深恶痛绝
by what you've done in her name.
我做的一切
What I have done?
我做的这一切
What I have done
都是你当初没胆去做的
is what you lack the courage to do!
你没胆为她而战
To fight for her!
所以
So...
当她横尸在你脚下
when her body lies at your feet,
当她的鲜血浸湿你的皮肤
her blood wet against your skin,
那时你就会明白我的感受
then you will know how I feel!
我已经明白你的感受了
I already know how you feel.
我知道仇恨是什么感觉
I know what it's like to hate.
复仇的渴望
To want revenge.
现在我也明白了眼看自己的敌人
And now I know how it feels
心烦意乱是什么感觉
to see my enemy so distracted,
他没有发现真正的危险就在他眼前
he doesn't see the real danger is right in front of him.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
明白
Yes.
杀了她
Kill her!
带她们离开这里
Get them out of here!
可怜的莎拉
Poor Sara.
你要看着她死多少次
How many times you going to watch her die?
你杀不了我
You can't kill me.
我并不是因为米拉库鲁才恨你
The Mirakuru isn't what made me hate you!
末日临近
The end is near.
但我也许会非常仁慈地
But maybe I'll be merciful enough
让你活下来  看着你的城市化为灰烬
to let you live and see your city burn!
我们都知道终结这一切
We both know there's only one way
只有一个办法
that this can end.
要打败我  小子
To beat me, kid,
你就必须杀了我
you're going to have to kill me.
但是在我死的那一刻
But in the moment of my death,
你将证明一件事
you'll prove one thing...
你是个凶手
that you are a murderer.
你打算怎么做  小子
What are you going to do, kid?
给我扎一剂解药吗
Stick me with the cure?
没关系
It doesn't matter.
我会信守我的誓言
I'll keep my promise!
我会带走你所珍爱的
I'll take away everything
所有事和所有人
and everyone you love!
莎拉只是第一个
Sara was only the first!
她只是第一个
She was only the first!
你的妹妹  劳蕾尔  你的母亲
Your sister, Laurel, your mother!
你可以杀了我  或者不杀我
You can kill me, or not.
不管怎样  我都赢了
Either way, I win.
阿曼达  结束了
Amanda, it's over.
斯莱德已被拿下  他的军队也被打败了
Slade's down, his army's been taken out.
召回无人机
Call back the drones.
阿曼达  结束了
Amanda, it's over!
现在你打算怎么办  小子
So what now, kid?
是时候了
It's time.
为  为什么他们逼你这么做
Why... why are they making you do this?
为什么你要逼她这么做  为什么
Why are you making her do this, huh? Why?
爸爸  她没有逼我做任何事
Dad, she's not making me do anything.
这是我自己的选择
I chose this.
我要怎么跟你妈妈说
What am I going to tell your mother?
告诉她  我有生以来第一次
Tell her that for the first time in my life,
能够自己决定自己的命运
I'm deciding my own fate.
她会理解的
She'll understand that.
我爱你  宝贝
I love you, sweetheart.
我也爱你  爸爸
I love you, too, dad.
我明白父爱的力量
I know the power of a father's love,
我会誓死保护你女儿的安全
and I would die before I let anything happen to your daughter.
希望如此吧
Well, here's hoping.
那么  你要去哪儿
So, where you're going,
你可以发电子邮件或者打电话吗
will you be able to email or call?
-我会跟你再见面的  -我知道
- I'll see you again. - I know.
如果说今年我有学到什么的话
If there's anything that I've learned this year,
那就是你总能知道怎么回家
it's that you always find your way home.
而我们也会一直等待着你
And we'll always be here waiting.
我爱你
I love you.
奥利弗需要你
Oliver needs you.
还有
And, hey...
我觉得这个穿在你身上会很好看
I think that this would look good on you.
很合身
It fits.
-再见  爸爸  -再见  宝贝
- Bye, dad. - Bye, sweetheart.
关于那件夹克
About that jacket...
不要有什么想法
Don't get any ideas.
咱俩应该开会讨论一下
I could really use a meeting.
没错  也许对咱俩都是个好主意
Yeah, probably a good idea for the both of us.
不过我路上要去买点胃药
Listen, I got to pick up a little Pepto on the way,
我感觉有点不舒服
though, 'cause I'm feeling kind of weird.
爸爸  她会没事的
Dad, she'll be ok.
我知道她没事  但我担心的就是她那种没事
Yeah, I know she'll be ok, but ok what is what bothers me.
爸爸
Dad?
Dad!
-天呐  -爸爸
- Oh, my God. - Dad!
爸爸
Dad!
天呐
Oh, my god!
我不能呼吸了
I can't get my breath!
我不能
I can't...
爸爸  坚持住  爸爸  坚持住
Dad, stay with me! Daddy, daddy, stay with me!
喂  我需要救护车
Hello, I need an ambulance.
我父亲是星城警署的  对  马上
My father's SCPD. Yes, now!
爸爸  坚持住
Daddy, stay with me!
西娅
Thea.
Thea!
罗伊  对不起
Roy...I'm sorry.
我犯错了
I made a mistake.
我以为我还能继续跟你在一起
I thought I could still be with you.
我以为我还能继续做西娅·奎恩
I thought I could still be Thea Queen.
但是西娅·奎恩很信任他人
But Thea Queen was trusting.
而我不信任你
And I don't trust you.
我不信任任何人  再也不会了
Or anyone. Not anymore.
西娅·奎恩软弱无能
Thea Queen was also weak.
无论如何  我都要变坚强
And no matter what it takes, I will be strong.
不要来找我  你找不到的
Don't try to find me. You won't.
我自己都不知道要去哪里
Even I don't know where I'm going.
我只知道一件事
I only know one thing...
我永远不会回来了
I am never coming back.
这是哪里
Where am I?
世界上最遥远的地方
As far away from the world as I could get you.
你无法伤害他人的地方
Where you can't hurt anyone ever again.
这就是你的弱点  小子
That's your weakness, kid.
你没胆量杀我
You don't have the guts to kill me.
不  我有勇气让你活着
No. I have the strength to let you live.
你是个杀手
You're a killer.
我知道  是我创造的你
I know, I created you.
你杀过很多人
You've killed plenty.
对  我是杀过
Yes, I have.
你在我需要的时候把我变成了杀手
You helped turn me into a killer when I needed to be one.
我今天还活着多亏了你
And I'm alive today because of you.
我能回家也多亏了你
I made it home because of you.
因此我才能再次见到我的家人
And I got to see my family again.
但是过去一年  我需要更加...
But over the past year, I've needed to be more...
可我退缩了
and I faltered.
但是后来我阻止了你
But then I stopped you.
而且没有杀你
Without killing.
你帮我变成了英雄  斯莱德
You helped me become a hero, Slade.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你以为我出不去吗
You think I won't get out of here?
你以为我不会杀那些你关心的人吗
You think I won't kill those you care for?
不会的  因为你在炼狱里
No, I don't. Because you're in purgatory.
我言出必行  小子
I keep my promises, kid.
我言出必行
I keep my promises!
I keep my promises.
上次没注意  其实这里挺漂亮的
Last time I didn't notice, it's actually kind of beautiful here.
不要误会  我一直在倒计时
Don't get me wrong, I'm counting down the seconds
准备离开这布满地雷的小岛呢
until we shove off minefield island.
你觉得这样能关住他吗
So you think that'll be enough to hold him,
用超能力联合调查组的超级监狱
A.R.G.U.S.' super max?
关他  还有我们送过来的其他人
Him, and anyone else we send here.
这场战争可能结束了  但以后的事还有很多
This battle may be over, but there will be others.
首先应该从夺回我的家族公司开始
Starting with getting my family's company back.
那可不容易  你现在没钱了
That's not going to be easy, since you're poor now.
你得先找份工作
You're going to have to get a job.
如果你没被斯莱德吓到的话
If Slade doesn't scare you, that's got to.
你知道有谁想雇个
Do you know anyone hiring ex-billionaires
射箭水平一流的前亿万富翁吗
with superior archery skills?
我说  要不我让你们
Hey, why don't I,
单独待一会儿吧
give you two a second?
你成功了
Well, you did it.
-有人帮我嘛  -对
- I had help. - Yeah.
你那招很聪明
That's really smart.
你终于赢过他了
How you out-foxed him.
说到没料到的事
Talk about unthinkable.
我是说  你跟我
You and me, I mean.
当你说你爱我的时候
When you told me you loved me,
你真骗倒我了  那一瞬间  我...
you had me fooled. For a second, I...
我以为你可能是真心的
maybe you might have meant it.
你跟我说的话
What you said.
你演得太好了
You really sold it.
我们都演得很好
We both did.
回家吧
Let's go home.
狄格  你跟莱拉怎么样了
Dig, what was the news about you and Lyla?
我们的事可以等等
It can wait.
-我来开飞机  -请便
- I'm flying. - Be my guest.
我还有个问题
I got one more question!
要是没问题就不像你了
Wouldn't be you if you didn't.
如果你在这座岛上待了五年
If you spent five years on this island,
那你是什么时候学会开飞机的
when did you learn how to fly a plane?
跟我来
我是阿曼达·沃勒  奎恩先生
My name is Amanda Waller, Mr. Queen.
我们有很多事要谈
We have a lot to discuss.
欢迎来香港
Welcome to Hong Kong.